Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
- Box: 81, Folder: 3 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Steel, Publication (Box 81, Folder 3)
    By Merrill Lynch, Pierce, Fenner & Beane. December 1945. Item is in English.
- Box: 81, Folder: 4 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: West Nomestead Hourly Employee Information, Publication (Box 81, Folder 4)
    By Mesta Machine Co. July 1, 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Hourly Employees' Group Insurance Program, Publication (Box 81, Folder 4)
    By Mesta Machine Co. As Amended Effective 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Savings and Vacation Plan For Hourlt Paid Employees of Mesta Machine Co. West Homestead Plant, Publication (Box 81, Folder 4)
    By Mesta Machine Co. effective December 31, 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Salaried Employees' 1974 Supplemental Vacation and Retirement Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 81, Folder 4)
    By Mesta Machine Co. Effective January 1, 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Salary Employees' Group Insurance Program, Publication (Box 81, Folder 4)
    By Mesta Machine Co. As Amended Effective October 1, 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan For Employees of Mesta Machine Co. West Homestead, Publication (Box 81, Folder 4)
    By Mesta Machine Co. Effective October 1, 1974; c.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan For Salaried Employees of Mesta Machine Co., Publication (Box 81, Folder 4)
    By Mesta Machine Co. Efective October 1, 1974; c.2. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Employee benefit Plans: Summary Plan Description, Publication (Box 81, Folder 4)
    By Mesta Machine Co. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Savings and Vacation Plan For Hourly Paid Employees of Mesta machine Co West Homestead Plant, Publication (Box 81, Folder 4)
    By Mesta Machine Co. Effective December 31, 1973; c.2. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Hourly Employees' Group Insurance Program, Publication (Box 81, Folder 4)
- Box: 81, Folder: 5 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Employee's Profit Sharing Plan, Publication (Box 81, Folder 5)
    By Metal Office Furniture Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 81, Folder: 6 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Church and the Social Question, Publication (Box 81, Folder 6)
    By The Methodist Church. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Christian Churchman in Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Register Christian Opinion!, Publication (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Board of World Peace, Publication (Box 81, Folder 6)
- Box: 81, Folder: 7 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Policy and Procedure, Publication (Box 81, Folder 7)
    By The Methodist Hospital. Item is in English.
- Box: 81, Folder: 8 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Labor Agreements, Publication (Box 81, Folder 8)
    By National Labor Bureau. Item is in English.
- Box: 81, Folder: 9 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Unfinished Business, Publication (Box 81, Folder 9)
    By Metropolitan Detroit Council on Fair Employment Practice. Item is in English.
- Box: 81, Folder: 10 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Methods of Compensation: A Practical Synopsis for Business Men, Publication (Box 81, Folder 10)
    By Metropolitan Life Insurance Company. Number One: Methods of Compensating Salesmen. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Methods of Compensation: A Practical Synopsis for Business Men, Publication (Box 81, Folder 10)
    By Metropolitan Life Insurance Company. Number Two: Analysis of Branch Managers' Contracts. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Methods of Compensation: A Practical Synopsis for Business Men, Publication (Box 81, Folder 10)
    By Metropolitan Life Insurance Company. Number Three: Methods of Paying Factory Workers. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Methods of Compensation: A Practical Synopsis for Business Men, Publication (Box 81, Folder 10)
    By Metropolitan Life Insurance Company. Number Four: Methods of Compensating Office Employees. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Methods of Compensation: A Practical Synopsis for Business Men, Publication (Box 81, Folder 10)
    By Metropolitan Life Insurance Company. Number Five: Methods of Compensating Drivers. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Methods of Compensation: A Practical Synopsis for Business Men, Publication (Box 81, Folder 10)
    By Metropolitan Life Insurance Company. Number Six: Methods of Compensating Retail Clerks. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Methods of Compensation: A Practical Synopsis for Business Men, Publication (Box 81, Folder 10)
    By Metropolitan Life Insurance Company. Number Seven: Methods of Compensating Production Executives. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: A Manual of Information, Rules and Suggestions, Publication (Box 81, Folder 10)
    By Metropolitan Life Insurance Company. for the guidance of Home Office Employees. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Health of the Worker: Dangers to Health in the Factory and Shop and How to Avoid Them, Publication (Box 81, Folder 10)
    By C.E.A. Winslow. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Foreman's Part in Safety, Publication (Box 81, Folder 10)
    By Metropolitan Life Insurance Company. Industry Safety Number 4: Methods of Enlisting Supervisory Support. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Insurance and Retirement Program for Agents in the United States, Publication (Box 81, Folder 10)
    By Metropolitan Life Insurance Company. July 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Retirement Annuity Plan of the New York Stock Exchange and its Affiliated Companies, Publication (Box 81, Folder 10)
    By New York Stock Exchange. March 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Steadying Business, Publication (Box 81, Folder 10)
    By Metropolitan Life Insurance Company. Number 2: The Metal Trades. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: equal employment opportunity at Metropolitan, Publication (Box 81, Folder 10)
    By Metropolitan Life Insurance Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: your Metropolitan Life, Publication (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: Workmen's Safety Committees, Publication (Box 81, Folder 10)
    By Metropolitan Life Insurance Company. Indutrial Safety Number 5: Methods of Organizing and Conducting Safety Committees. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Employee Performance Report, Publication (Box 81, Folder 10)
    By Metropolitan Life Insurance Company. Nonsupervisory. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Employee Opinion Survey Questionnaire, Publication (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: The Use of Psychological Tests in the Selection of Office Employees, Publication (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Item 20: Information Manuals for Employees, Publication (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Item 21: Salary Standardization and Administration, Publication (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Item 22: The Older Employee in Industry, Publication (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Item 23: Outline for a Management Augist, Publication (Box 81, Folder 10)
- Box: 81, Folder: 11 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Telling Employees About Business Operations: Profits, Publication (Box 81, Folder 11)
    By Policyholders Service Bureau. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Control of Labor Turnover, Publication (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Training Employees As Job Instructors: A Method for Facilitating War Production, Publication (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Training College Graduates for Management, Publication (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Training Salesmen, Publication (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Training Supervisors In Human Relations, Publication (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Training Chain Store Sales Personnel, Publication (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Training Employees As Job Instructors: A Method for Facilitating War Production, Publication (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Operation Study, Publication (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: The Welfare Work of the Metropolitan Life Insurance Company Reports for 1914, Publication (Box 81, Folder 11)
    By Lee K. Frankel. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Welfare Work of the Metropolitan Life Insurance Company For Its Employees: Reports for 1917, Publication (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Item 12: The Welfare Work of the Metropolitan Life Insurance Copmany For Its Employees: Reports For 1918, Publication (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Item 13: Welfare Work Conducted by the Metropolitan Life Insurance Company for the Benefit of its Employees, Publication (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Item 14: Welfare Work Conducted by the Metropolitan Life Insurance Company for the Benefit of its Industrial Policy-holders, Publication (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Item 15: Personnel Leaflets - No. 5: The Job Blueprint, Publication (Box 81, Folder 11)
    By Personnel Division for the Policyholders Service Bureau. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Hand Manuals of Standard Employment Practice, Number One: The Job Specification, Publication (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Item 17: Labor Turnover Series No. 2: The Exit Interview, Publication (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Item 18: Labor Turnover Series No. 3: The Foreman and Labor Turnover, Publication (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Item 19: Labor Turnover Series No. 4: How High Should Labor Turnover Be?, Publication (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Item 20: The Welfare Work Conducted by the Metropolitan Life Insurance Company for the Benefits of its Industrial Policy-holders, Publication (Box 81, Folder 11)
    By Policholders Service Bureau. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Indutrial Pensions or the Care of Faithful Workers, Publication (Box 81, Folder 11)
    By James E. Kavanaugh. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Old Age Pension Plan Group Pension Bonds, Publication (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Item 23: Metropolitan Life Insurance Company Tuberculosis Sanatorium for Employees, Publication (Box 81, Folder 11)
- Box: 81, Folder: 12 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Metropolitan Transit Authority Retirement Fund, Publication (Box 81, Folder 12)
    By Metropolitan Transit Authority. Item is in English.
- Box: 81, Folder: 13 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Grief Process: Some Implications for Nursing Practice, Publication (Box 81, Folder 13)
    By Michigan Nurses Association. Item is in English.
- Box: 81, Folder: 14 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Crisis in American Unionism, Publication (Box 81, Folder 14)
    By Edwin E. White. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Fair Wages and Economic Stability, Publication (Box 81, Folder 14)
    By C.E. Wilson. Item is in English.
- Box: 81, Folder: 15 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Indirect Workers, Publication (Box 81, Folder 15)
    By University of Michigan. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Human Relations Study Techniques, Publication (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: An Experiment in Community Improvement, Publication (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: United Steel Workers of America, Publication (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Workers Educational Service, Publication (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Supplemental Unemployment Benefits: Principles and Problems, Publication (Box 81, Folder 15)
    By Richard A. Leutheuser. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Appraisal of Employee Performance, Publication (Box 81, Folder 15)
    By Algie A. Hendrix; Byron Stewart. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The 1955 Ford-UAW Contract, Publication (Box 81, Folder 15)
    By John J. DeMott, Jr. Item is in English.
- Box: 81, Folder: 16 (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Western Michigan University Performance Review Program, Publication (Box 81, Folder 16)
    By University Personnel Department. Folder with various memos and report. Item is in English.
- Box: 81, Folder: 17 (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Employees' Pension Plan, Publication (Box 81, Folder 17)
    By Midvale Steel & Ordnance Co.: Personnel Services. Effective July 1, 1919. Item is in English.
- Box: 81, Folder: 18 (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Comparison of Provisions: Walter-Mc Carran Law and Lehman-Celler Bill, Publication (Box 81, Folder 18)
    By American Committee for Protection of Foreign Born. Item is in English.
- Box: 81, Folder: 19 (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: The Military Training Camps Association of the United States, Publication (Box 81, Folder 19)
    By Military Training Camps Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Military Training Camps Association of the United States, Publication (Box 81, Folder 19)
    By George James. February 28, 1924. Item is in English.
- Box: 81, Folder: 20 (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Your New Job, Publication (Box 81, Folder 20)
    By Minneapolis: Honeywell Co. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Wage and Salary Administration, Publication (Box 81, Folder 20)
- Box: 81, Folder: 21 (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: How Your Pay is Determined at Minneapolis Moline, Publication (Box 81, Folder 21)
    By Minneapolis Moline. June 17, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Minneapolis Moline Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 81, Folder 21)
    By Minneapolis Moline. As amended, Oct. 1, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: A Group Insurance Program for your Dependents, Publication (Box 81, Folder 21)
    By Minneapolis Moline. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Minneapolis Moline Pension Plan for Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: Old Timers' Club: Souvenir Booklet, Publication (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - Item 6: Prairie Gold, Publication (Box 81, Folder 21)
    By Minneapolis Moline. September, 1949; Newspaper article. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Prairie Gold: Special Father-Son Issue, Publication (Box 81, Folder 21)
    By Minneapolis Moline. September, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Your Minneapolis Moline Guide, Publication (Box 81, Folder 21)
    By Minneapolis Moline. Revised March 15, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Wage Policy and Procedure for Office, Clerical and Technical Employees, Publication (Box 81, Folder 21)
    By Minneapolis Moline. November 21, 1946. Item is in English.
- Box: 81, Folder: 22 (Box 81, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Your Minneapolis Moline Guide, Publication (Box 81, Folder 22)
    By Minneapolis Moline. Revised February 15, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Management Policy Manual, Publication (Box 81, Folder 22)
    By Minneapolis Moline. October 5, 1948. Item is in English.
- Box: 82, Folder: 1 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Supervisor's Manual, Publication (Box 82, Folder 1)
    By 3M (Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing). Item is in English.
- Box: 82, Folder: 2 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Your Short Term Disability Benefits, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Your Long Term Disability Benefits, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: General Profit Sharing Plan, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: your hidden bank accounts, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Safety Guide, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: General Performance Review, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Salary Administration Policy, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: The House that Research, Quality, and Sales Built, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Safety Digest, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
    By H. P. Bueton. August 14, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Safety Digest, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
    By 3M (Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing). September 14, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Safety Digest, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
    By 3M (Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing). October 1, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: 3M Megaphone, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
    By 3M (Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing). v.2:no.10 (1959:May 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: 3M Megaphone, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
    By 3M (Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing). v.13:no.4 (1953:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: 3M Megaphone, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
    By 3M (Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing). v.8:no.4 (1968:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 15: 3M Tartan, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
    By 3M (Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing). no.2 (1967). Item is in English.
  - Item 16: 3M Tartan, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
    By 3M (Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing). no.3 (1967). Item is in English.
  - Item 17: 3M Tartan, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
    By 3M (Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing). no.1 (1968). Item is in English.
  - Item 18: More protection, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: Your 3M Pension, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: Report on the Production Training Department, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: Company Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Item 22: Organizational Chart, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
    By 3M (Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing). January 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: International Operations, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
    By 3M (Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing). April 2, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Historical Sketch, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Item 25: Nearly everyone knows 3M, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Item 26: The Second Most Important Thing in your Life, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Item 27: This is 3M Company, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
- Box: 82, Folder: 3 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Rules and Regulations For Proceedings Under Minnesota Labor Relations Act, Publication (Box 82, Folder 3)
    By Division of Conciliation State of Minnesota. Item is in English.
- Box: 82, Folder: 4 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Industrial Relations Center of the University of Minnesota, Publication (Box 82, Folder 4)
    By University of Minnesota Minneapolis. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Minnesota Business News, Publication (Box 82, Folder 4)
    By School of Business Administration. no.10 (1963:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Minnesota Business News, Publication (Box 82, Folder 4)
    By School of Business Administration. no.11 (1963:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Minnesota Business News, Publication (Box 82, Folder 4)
    By School of Business Administration. no.12 (1963:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Minnesota Business News, Publication (Box 82, Folder 4)
    By School of Business Administration. no.13 (1963:Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Minnesota Business News, Publication (Box 82, Folder 4)
    By School of Business Administration. no.15 (1964:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Minnesota Business News, Publication (Box 82, Folder 4)
    By School of Business Administration. no.16 (1964:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Minnesota Business News, Publication (Box 82, Folder 4)
    By School of Business Administration. no.17 (1964:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Minnesota Business News, Publication (Box 82, Folder 4)
    By School of Business Administration. no.18 (1964:Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Minnesota Business News, Publication (Box 82, Folder 4)
    By School of Business Administration. no.19 (1965:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Minnesota Business News, Publication (Box 82, Folder 4)
    By School of Business Administration. no.20 (1965:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Minnesota Business News, Publication (Box 82, Folder 4)
    By School of Business Administration. no.21 (1965:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Minnesota Business News, Publication (Box 82, Folder 4)
    By School of Business Administration. no.22 (1965:Sep.). Item is in English.
- Box: 82, Folder: 5 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Letter to Mr. Collins, Publication (Box 82, Folder 5)
    By John W. Barringer. Received Nune 15,1965 International Headquarters ,. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Some press reactions to first inspection trip and on-line visits made by: John W. Barriger President Missouri-Kansas-Texas Railroad Company, Publication (Box 82, Folder 5)
    March-April- May, 19655. Item is in English.
- Box: 82, Folder: 6 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Schedule of Wages: Locomotive Engineers, Publication (Box 82, Folder 6)
    By Missouri Pacific Railroad Co. Rules Effective September 1, 1930, Rates Effectice April 1, 1944, Reprint January 1, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Missouri Pacific Lines News, Publication (Box 82, Folder 6)
    By Missouri Pacific News Bureau. For Release at 12 O'Clock Noon, May 18, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Missouri Pacific Lines News, Publication (Box 82, Folder 6)
    By Missouri Pacific News Bureau. For Release at 12 o'clock Noon, Thursday, April 2nd, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Missouri Pacific Lines News Reel: Saint Louis -- September 1962, Publication (Box 82, Folder 6)
    By Missouri Pacific News Bureau. Item is in English.
- Box: 82, Folder: 7 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Fire Prevention at Mobil, Publication (Box 82, Folder 7)
    By Leonard O. Franklin. October, 26, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: We Want You to Live, Publication (Box 82, Folder 7)
    By Nicholas L. Bristow. October, 26, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Newsletter, Publication (Box 82, Folder 7)
    By National Safety Congress. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Newsletter, Publication (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: U.S. Business Abroad and the Voluntary Balance of Payments Program, Publication (Box 82, Folder 7)
    By George F. James. A talk before the National Industrial Conference Board's conference on "International Financing 1965". Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Major Current Environmental Acitivites, Publication (Box 82, Folder 7)
    By Mobil. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Move up with Mobil, Publication (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Mobil Guide for Press and Public Relations During Emergencies, Publication (Box 82, Folder 7)
    By Mobil Oil Corporation. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Importance of Completed Staff Work, Publication (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Mobil Sales Management: A Career For You, Publication (Box 82, Folder 7)
    By Mobil Oil Corporation. CF Training: Mobil Oil Corporation 368705. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: A Primer on Air Pollution, Publication (Box 82, Folder 7)
    By Mobil Oil Corporation. CF Safety; Mobil Oil Corp. 368700. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: 100 little driving blunders, Publication (Box 82, Folder 7)
    By Mobil Oil Corporation. CF Safety; Mobil Oil Corp 368701. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: How to Clean the Air: A Message for George Webster: Help!, Publication (Box 82, Folder 7)
    By Mobil Oil Corporation. CF Safety: Mobil Oil Corporation 368692; A reprint from the June 1967 issue of Mobil World, a worldwide newspaper for Mobil Employees. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Matching Gifts to Education Program, Publication (Box 82, Folder 7)
    By Mobil Foundation Inc. CF Personell Services 368676. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Mobil Merit Scholarship Program: For children of Mobil employees and annuitants, Publication (Box 82, Folder 7)
    By Mobil Oil Corporation. CF Personnel Services Mobil Oil Corporation 368675. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: To All Mobil Employees, Publication (Box 82, Folder 7)
    By Rawleigh Warner, jr. CF General Mobil Oil Corp 368625. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Mobil World: Two-Year Effort Lands Largest Nuclear Plant, Publication (Box 82, Folder 7)
    By Mobil Oil Corporation. CF Communications Mobil Oil Corporation 368663; Vol. 33 No. 8-9. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Mobil Annuitant Newsletter, Publication (Box 82, Folder 7)
    By Mobil Oil Corporation. January 1972. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Mobil: the Second Century, Publication (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Item 20: Extra Dimensions, Publication (Box 82, Folder 7)
    By Mobil Corporation; Rawleigh Warner, JR. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Chain of Command Chart, Publication (Box 82, Folder 7)
    By Mobil Corporation. Mobil Oil Corporation Handbooks, Manuals, etc. 00134. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Treat Your Fuels., Your Equipment, Your Vehicles, As If They Can KillThey Can, Publication (Box 82, Folder 7)